Guide to the Lawrence Langner Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Material Formerly Part of the Theatre Guild Archive, 1914-1983; Series III; 9.43; (22 boxes)
  - Oversize, 1934
    - The Importance of Wearing Clothes, undated; 3 (Box 110 (Oversize))
    - Unsorted photographs, undated (Box 110 (Oversize))
    - The Importance of Wearing Clothes, undated; 8 (Box 111 (Oversize))
    - The Pursuit of Happiness, 1934 (Box 112 (Oversize))
    - The Importance of Wearing Clothes, undated; 2 (Box 113 (Oversize))
    - Photo album, undated (Box 114 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbook, undated (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - The Importance of Wearing Clothes, undated; 5 (Box 116 (Oversize))
    - The Importance of Wearing Clothes, undated; 3 (Box 117 (Oversize))
    - The Magic Curtain, undated (Box 119 (Broadside))
  - Restricted Fragile
    Conditions Governing Access
    Resgricted fragile. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
    - The Magic Curtain, 1948, undated (Box 118)
      20 SoundScriber discs
- Material Formerly Classed as MS Vault Shelves Shaw, 1921-1948; Series IV; 0.42; (1 box)
  Includes correspondence between Bernard Shaw and Lawrence Langner relating to the production of Shaw's plays by the Theatre Guild; proofs of several Shaw plays; and a typescript article by Shaw.
  - Correspondence between Bernard Shaw and Lawrence Langner regarding Back to Methuselah, bound, 1921-1922 (Box 120)
  - Correspondence between Bernard Shaw and Lawrence Langner regarding St. Joan, bound, 1923-1924 (Box 120)
  - Back to Methuselah by Bernard Shaw, uncorrected proofs, bound with inscription from Shaw to Langner, 1921 February (Box 120)
  - Geneva by Bernard Shaw, "Rehearsal copy-Unpublished," privately printed, annotated; with inscription from Shaw to Langner, 1938 June (Box 120)
  - Geneva playscript by Bernard Shaw, "Second rehearsal copy, revsied after Bombardine's conversion to anti-Semitism;" privately printed, 1938 September (Box 120)
  - St. Joan: A Chronicle Play by Bernard Shaw, "rough proof-unpublished;" "latest version, Dec. 6, 1923," with annotations (Box 120)
  - "Wanted: A New Sort of Theatre for an Old Sort of Play," by Bernard Shaw, typescript with corrections and annotations, undated (Box 120)